<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:cmd0="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/" xmlns:cmd1="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/1"
    xmlns:datacite="http://purl.org/spar/datacite/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/terms/"
    xmlns:fabio="http://purl.org/spar/fabio/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#"
    xmlns:silvio="http://www.essepuntato.it/2010/06/literalreification/"
    xmlns:vlo="http://www.clarin.eu/vlo/">
    <fabio:Dataset rdf:about="oai_www_mpi_nl_lat_1839_00_0000_0000_0000_30B0_2.rdf"/>
    <fabio:Work rdf:about="oai_www_mpi_nl_lat_1839_00_0000_0000_0000_30B0_2.rdf">
        <datacite:hasIdentifier>
            <datacite:Identifier>
                <datacite:usesIdentifierScheme rdf:resource="http://purl.org/spar/datacite/handle"/>
                <silvio:hasLiteralValue>https://hdl.handle.net/1839/00-0000-0000-0000-30B0-2</silvio:hasLiteralValue>
            </datacite:Identifier>
        </datacite:hasIdentifier>
        <dc:abstract>MPI Project Temporality - Experiment description MPI Project Temporality -
            Legend Stimuli Description of the "Lamp" experiment Children were asked to carry out two
            tasks: 1. To watch a short clip on a laptop, which shows lamps being switched on and off
            in a particular temporal constellation (see stimuli) 2. After watching the clip,
            childern had to act-out the clip by using real lamps standing on a table in front of
            them. 3. The last task was to verbalize the temporal constellation in the movie shown to
            them. The order of tasks number (2) and (3) were counterbalanced. That is, half of the
            children acted-out before they retold the stimulus and half of the children first
            verbalized the content of the clip and then acted-out. In all cases, children were
            watching the stimulus together with the chief investigator and acted-out and retold it
            to an assistant who was also present in the room. The assistant, however, did not watch
            the stimulus. The child was asked to inform the assistant about the content of the clip
            so that she could imagine what it was about. In this manner, the child was motivated to
            be as specific as possible. MPI Project Temporality - Language Acquisition
            Group</dc:abstract>
        <dc:title>Barbsch L1</dc:title>
    </fabio:Work>
</rdf:RDF>
